that I would never get rid of.
But even with all the tracking in the world, none of the millionaires I know would make it anywhere without this last habit, which brings us to habit number seven, default to action. I have people talk to me all the time about starting their next thing, starting their first thing, and they always put it off. They wait until the situation is perfect. The truth is it's not about making the right decision, it's about making any decision and then making it right. Here's how much I personally believe in taking action when you know it's on your heart. In 2012, my company Flowtown was bought by Demand Force, and I had to stick around for 12 months, it's called your earn out, so that I received the full amount that they bought me for. Yet after a few months of being there, I came up with a new idea, this concept called clarity. And I knew on my heart I really wanted to do that, but I also knew leaving was kind of a dumb financial decision. But I decided after seven weeks of working on that idea that I had to go do it. After three months, I not only raised 1.6 million in funding, Demand Force got acquired by Intuit
But even with all the tracking in
the world,
none of the millionaires I know would
make it anywhere
without this last habit,
which brings us to habit number seven,
default to action.
I have people talk to me all
the time
about starting their next thing,
starting their first thing, and they always
put it off.
They wait until the situation is perfect.
The truth is it's not about making
the right decision,
it's about making any decision and then
making it right.
Here's how much I personally believe
in taking action when you know it's
on your heart.
In 2012, my company Flowtown was bought
by Demand Force,
and I had to stick around for
12 months,
it's called your earn out,
#it's #about #making #would
so that I received the full amount
Follow for more creator breakdowns
that they bought me for.